<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Christianity on Ranting Robert</title>
    <link>/tags/christianity/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Christianity on Ranting Robert</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© This post is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License，please give source if you likes to quote or reproduce.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/christianity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Three F&#39;s</title>
      <link>/post/the-three-f-s/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-three-f-s/</guid>
      <description>Another Thanksgiving has come and gone here in America. And for another year, this great holiday where we are to be thankful for what God has provided us with has once again fallen into commercialization. Thanksgiving has devolved into the three F&#39;s:
Food, Family, and Football
People flocked to places near and far to gather together with family members (along with a few friends) to prepare and enjoy a scrumptious feast consisting of one plate (or two, three, or sometimes four) plates of food.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Da Beats, Vol. 1</title>
      <link>/post/da-beats-vol-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/da-beats-vol-1/</guid>
      <description>I’m sure most of us have some hobbies that we do on the side. Some are things people know about and allow us to indulge in. Others include hidden sides that few, if any, may know. For me, this hidden side is poetry. I engaged in it little when I was in high school and college but have put it off to the side for a few years. However, I’ve come up with a few pieces recently that I would like to share.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When Freedom of Speech is No Longer Free</title>
      <link>/post/when-freedom-of-speech-is-no-longer-free/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/when-freedom-of-speech-is-no-longer-free/</guid>
      <description>Note: This is NOT an endorsement on the comments made by Los Angeles Clippers owner Donald Sterling.
So Clippers owner Donald Sterling was fined $2.5 million and banned from the NBA for life. There wasn’t even as much as a hint of an investigation before this was handed down. What did he do to warrant this harsh punishment? Did he beat his wife? Did he kill someone? Is he a serial rapist?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>