<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Obama on Ranting Robert</title>
    <link>/tags/obama/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Obama on Ranting Robert</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© This post is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License. Please source if you like to quote or reproduce.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/obama/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Bernie Sanders, Millennials, and Why They Are Wrong...About Everything</title>
      <link>/post/bernie-sanders-millennials-and-why-they-are-wrong-about-everything/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/bernie-sanders-millennials-and-why-they-are-wrong-about-everything/</guid>
      <description>Some of you are going to love this post. Most of you will hate it. My job is to ell the truth. Sometimes the truth hurts, and some of you can&#39;t handle the truth. However, the truth shall set you free. I&#39;m out of clichés.
Bernie Sanders is an admitted &amp;ldquo;democratic socialist&amp;rdquo;. There used to be a time not that long ago where socialism was proven to be a very bad thing in America and one step away from communism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More Radical Islamic Terrorism</title>
      <link>/post/more-radical-islamic-terrorism/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/more-radical-islamic-terrorism/</guid>
      <description>Over two years ago, I wrote a post after an attack in London in regards to radical Islam. I called out President Obama for not calling out radical Islam. He refuses to use those words. In fact, he referred to ISIS as a JV team in 2014. Even after the Charlie Hebdo attack in January 2015, President Obama refused to acknowledge that the real problem isn&#39;t the people, but the religion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I&#39;m a Conservative</title>
      <link>/post/why-i-m-a-conservative/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/why-i-m-a-conservative/</guid>
      <description>So some of my friends have criticized me for being a conservative. They go on to site how much damage and suffering African-Americans have gone through because of conservatives or how conservatives are made up of rich, racist, old white men. Or they complain about conservatives clinging to their guns and Bibles and having “outdated” morals and traditions.
Nothing can be further from the truth.
I’m a conservative because I am against big government.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>