<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>1st Amendment on Ranting Robert</title>
    <link>/tags/1st-amendment/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 1st Amendment on Ranting Robert</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© This post is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License. Please source if you like to quote or reproduce.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/1st-amendment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Purpose of the Press</title>
      <link>/post/purpose-of-the-press/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/purpose-of-the-press/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Congress shall make no law respecting an establishment of religion, or prohibiting the free exercise thereof; or abridging the freedom of speech, or of the press; or the right of the people peaceably to assemble, and to petition the Government for a redress of grievances.&amp;rdquo;
 Most of you should recognize that as the First Amendment to the United States Constitution. A lot of power and responsibility is recognized in that sentence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Pointless Debate</title>
      <link>/post/the-pointless-debate/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-pointless-debate/</guid>
      <description>Over the last 10-20 years, I have had many heated political discussions with people of different colors, different backgrounds, and different walks of life. Social media has made it easier to have these discussions and meet all kinds of people. When having such discussions, my goal is to be as clear minded and rational as possible when arguing my point of view while trying to use as much anecdotal evidence as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Safe Spaces</title>
      <link>/post/safe-spaces/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/safe-spaces/</guid>
      <description>Safe Space: A place where anyone can relax and be fully self-expressed, without fear of being made to feel uncomfortable, unwelcome, or unsafe on account of biological sex, race/ethnicity, sexual orientation, gender identity or expression, cultural background, age, or physical or mental ability; a place where the rules guard each person&#39;s self-respect and dignity and strongly encourage everyone to respect others
 WHAT??!!!!
Where did this come from and why are these popping up all over college campuses in America?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Role of the Media in 21st Century America</title>
      <link>/post/the-role-of-the-media-in-21st-century-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-role-of-the-media-in-21st-century-america/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Congress shall make no law respecting an establishment of religion, or prohibiting the free exercise thereof; or abridging the freedom of speech, or of the press; or the right of the people peaceably to assemble, and to petition the Government for a redress of grievances.&amp;rdquo;
  1st Amendment of the United States Constitution
 That&#39;s a mouthful right there. I&#39;m not going to go into detail as to what all of this means.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>