<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>election on Ranting Robert</title>
    <link>/tags/election/</link>
    <description>Recent content in election on Ranting Robert</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© This post is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License，please give source if you likes to quote or reproduce.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/election/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Do You Really Want Another President Clinton?</title>
      <link>/post/do-you-really-want-another-president-clinton/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/do-you-really-want-another-president-clinton/</guid>
      <description>Really? This #NeverTrump movement by fellow conservatives is getting out of hand. Do you realize at this point is that your only real options are Donald Trump and Hillary Clinton?
Look, I get it. I&#39;m not a Trump guy myself. My first choice was Ben Carson, my second choice was Ted Cruz. They were a couple of solid conservatives who would have brought reason, common sense, and strong morals back to the White House.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uninformed or Uncaring</title>
      <link>/post/uninformed-or-uncaring/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/uninformed-or-uncaring/</guid>
      <description>NOTE: THIS IS NOT AN ENDORSEMENT OF THE DEMOCRATIC PARTY!
Let me get this straight. The City of Pittsburgh has a population of 307,000. There are 175,000 Democrats who outnumber Republicans 5 to 1. In a city that has been ran by the Democratic Party for over half a century, only 44,000 turned out. That’s 25%. Bill Peduto won the Democratic nomination with 52% of the vote. 22,800 voters is only 13% of the total number of registered Democrats.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>