<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>news on Ranting Robert</title>
    <link>/tags/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in news on Ranting Robert</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© This post is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License. Please source if you like to quote or reproduce.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Wendy Bell and the Outrage of Black Pittsburgh</title>
      <link>/post/wendy-bell-and-the-outrage-of-black-pittsburgh/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/wendy-bell-and-the-outrage-of-black-pittsburgh/</guid>
      <description>Trigger Warning: This post contains truthful information that may be offensive or sensitive to certain segments of the population such as college students, liberals, and blacks. I am not responsible for any hurt feelings this may cause. Of course, I don&#39;t care about your feelings.
Pittsburgh reporter Wendy Bell was [fired from WTAE] (https://www.post-gazette.com/ae/tv-radio/2016/03/30/WTAE-TV-s-Wendy-Bell-fired-over-racially-inflammatory-messages/stories/201603300196) after making some controversial remarks on her Facebook page after a recent shooting. As we all know, when we talk about controversy and black people, it usually means black people don&#39;t like what someone else said about them because it&#39;s the truth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do Black Lives Matter?</title>
      <link>/post/do-black-lives-matter/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/do-black-lives-matter/</guid>
      <description>I don&#39;t watch shows like Family Guy, The Simpsons, South Park, etc. They&#39;re usually full of trash and (mostly) liberal propaganda. However, even a blind squirrel can find a nut every once in a while. A clip from an episode of Family Guy went viral last month.
 Peter Griffin: Everyone! Everyone! Listen, I have something to say. Cleveland Jr. Doesn&#39;t deserve any of this. All those things you heard about Cleveland Jr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Role of the Media in 21st Century America</title>
      <link>/post/the-role-of-the-media-in-21st-century-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-role-of-the-media-in-21st-century-america/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Congress shall make no law respecting an establishment of religion, or prohibiting the free exercise thereof; or abridging the freedom of speech, or of the press; or the right of the people peaceably to assemble, and to petition the Government for a redress of grievances.&amp;rdquo;
  1st Amendment of the United States Constitution
 That&#39;s a mouthful right there. I&#39;m not going to go into detail as to what all of this means.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>