<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hillary Clinton on Ranting Robert</title>
    <link>/tags/hillary-clinton/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hillary Clinton on Ranting Robert</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© This post is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License，please give source if you likes to quote or reproduce.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/hillary-clinton/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>American Ignorance</title>
      <link>/post/american-ignorance/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/american-ignorance/</guid>
      <description>Let me see if I got this right. If I were to ever stand with #BlackLivesMatter, I would get a ton of likes. When I post #BlueLivesMatter or #AllLivesMatter, I have condemnation in a conversation thread a mile long. Talking about #PokemonGo would get me a ton of likes.
Yet talking about Hillary Clinton lying to the FBI gets silence. Talking about Radical Islamic terrorism &amp;ndash; the biggest issue of our time &amp;ndash; gets silence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do You Really Want Another President Clinton?</title>
      <link>/post/do-you-really-want-another-president-clinton/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/do-you-really-want-another-president-clinton/</guid>
      <description>Really? This #NeverTrump movement by fellow conservatives is getting out of hand. Do you realize at this point is that your only real options are Donald Trump and Hillary Clinton?
Look, I get it. I&amp;rsquo;m not a Trump guy myself. My first choice was Ben Carson, my second choice was Ted Cruz. They were a couple of solid conservatives who would have brought reason, common sense, and strong morals back to the White House.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bernie Sanders, Millennials, and Why They Are Wrong...About Everything</title>
      <link>/post/bernie-sanders-millennials-and-why-they-are-wrong-about-everything/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/bernie-sanders-millennials-and-why-they-are-wrong-about-everything/</guid>
      <description>Some of you are going to love this post. Most of you will hate it. My job is to ell the truth. Sometimes the truth hurts, and some of you can&amp;rsquo;t handle the truth. However, the truth shall set you free. I&amp;rsquo;m out of clichés.
Bernie Sanders is an admitted &amp;ldquo;democratic socialist&amp;rdquo;. There used to be a time not that long ago where socialism was proven to be a very bad thing in America and one step away from communism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Corruption of the DNC</title>
      <link>/post/the-corruption-of-the-dnc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-corruption-of-the-dnc/</guid>
      <description>Hillary Clinton, Martin O&amp;rsquo;Malley, and Bernie Sanders&amp;hellip;three people who will never be president
Disclaimer: I am NOT a Democrat. I am not endorsing any Democrats at all. I am not supporting Hillary Clinton, Bernie Sanders, and Martin O&amp;rsquo;Malley and I hope the Democratic nominee gets destroyed in the general election. None of them are capable of fixing this country.
Now that the disclaimer is out of the way&amp;hellip;
Bernie Sanders is getting screwed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Role of the Media in 21st Century America</title>
      <link>/post/the-role-of-the-media-in-21st-century-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-role-of-the-media-in-21st-century-america/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Congress shall make no law respecting an establishment of religion, or prohibiting the free exercise thereof; or abridging the freedom of speech, or of the press; or the right of the people peaceably to assemble, and to petition the Government for a redress of grievances.&amp;rdquo;
1st Amendment of the United States Constitution
 That&amp;rsquo;s a mouthful right there. I&amp;rsquo;m not going to go into detail as to what all of this means.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Truth Shall Come Out</title>
      <link>/post/the-truth-shall-come-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-truth-shall-come-out/</guid>
      <description>So a select committee has finally been formed to investigate Benghazi…20 months and one Presidential election after the attack. There are STILL questions that we are still awaiting honest answers for. I think the family members of the victims deserve answers more. In no particular order:
Why did we still have people in Benghazi after every other foreign entity, including the Red Cross, left due to safety concerns?
Why was security not increased after previous attacks on the consulate in April 2012 and on the International Red Cross office in May 2012?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>