<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Ranting Robert</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Ranting Robert</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© This post is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License，please give source if you likes to quote or reproduce.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Resistant to Change</title>
      <link>/post/resistant-to-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/resistant-to-change/</guid>
      <description>I thought &amp;ldquo;Hope and Change&amp;rdquo; was the name of the game in 2008. So why are you so resistant and allergic to change now? Is it because you don&amp;rsquo;t want the changes? Maybe you don&amp;rsquo;t like the changes. Was this not what you wanted?
The reality is that the United States federal government is both broke and broken. Yet anytime President Donald Trump (Still hurts, doesn&amp;rsquo;t it?) proposes some kind of change to try to get our house in order, the Democrats in Congress, most leftists, and most of the mainstream media poo-poo all over it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Power of Roger Goodell</title>
      <link>/post/the-power-of-roger-goodell/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-power-of-roger-goodell/</guid>
      <description>When Roger Goodell succeeded Paul Tagliabue as NFL commissioner in 2006, players getting into trouble off the field was become a major problem. With players like Adam &amp;ldquo;Pacman&amp;rdquo; Jones and Chris Henry getting arrested every other week and a multitude of other players committing various legal infractions going unpunished by the league, it appeared as though a firm hand was needed. Long-term suspensions for Jones and Henry in 2007 seemed to send a message that improper behavior was no longer tolerated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>American Ignorance</title>
      <link>/post/american-ignorance/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/american-ignorance/</guid>
      <description>Let me see if I got this right. If I were to ever stand with #BlackLivesMatter, I would get a ton of likes. When I post #BlueLivesMatter or #AllLivesMatter, I have condemnation in a conversation thread a mile long. Talking about #PokemonGo would get me a ton of likes.
Yet talking about Hillary Clinton lying to the FBI gets silence. Talking about Radical Islamic terrorism &amp;ndash; the biggest issue of our time &amp;ndash; gets silence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Purpose of the Press</title>
      <link>/post/purpose-of-the-press/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/purpose-of-the-press/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Congress shall make no law respecting an establishment of religion, or prohibiting the free exercise thereof; or abridging the freedom of speech, or of the press; or the right of the people peaceably to assemble, and to petition the Government for a redress of grievances.&amp;rdquo;
 Most of you should recognize that as the First Amendment to the United States Constitution. A lot of power and responsibility is recognized in that sentence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do You Really Want Another President Clinton?</title>
      <link>/post/do-you-really-want-another-president-clinton/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/do-you-really-want-another-president-clinton/</guid>
      <description>Really? This #NeverTrump movement by fellow conservatives is getting out of hand. Do you realize at this point is that your only real options are Donald Trump and Hillary Clinton?
Look, I get it. I&amp;rsquo;m not a Trump guy myself. My first choice was Ben Carson, my second choice was Ted Cruz. They were a couple of solid conservatives who would have brought reason, common sense, and strong morals back to the White House.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wendy Bell and the Outrage of Black Pittsburgh</title>
      <link>/post/wendy-bell-and-the-outrage-of-black-pittsburgh/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/wendy-bell-and-the-outrage-of-black-pittsburgh/</guid>
      <description>Trigger Warning: This post contains truthful information that may be offensive or sensitive to certain segments of the population such as college students, liberals, and blacks. I am not responsible for any hurt feelings this may cause. Of course, I don&amp;rsquo;t care about your feelings.
Pittsburgh reporter Wendy Bell was fired from WTAE after making some controversial remarks on her Facebook page after a recent shooting. As we all know, when we talk about controversy and black people, it usually means black people don&amp;rsquo;t like what someone else said about them because it&amp;rsquo;s the truth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Martavis?  Why?</title>
      <link>/post/why-martavis-why/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/why-martavis-why/</guid>
      <description>Once upon a time, there was a wide receiver who was very talented physically but had some issues of the field. He liked to smoke marijuana in his free time. An NFL team decided to take a chance on him and he was able to put up big numbers on the field as a rookie. However, he was suspended for a few games before his second year in the league. The troubled wide receiver promised to clean up his act and returned to dominating on the field after returning for suspension.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Pointless Debate</title>
      <link>/post/the-pointless-debate/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-pointless-debate/</guid>
      <description>Over the last 10-20 years, I have had many heated political discussions with people of different colors, different backgrounds, and different walks of life. Social media has made it easier to have these discussions and meet all kinds of people. When having such discussions, my goal is to be as clear minded and rational as possible when arguing my point of view while trying to use as much anecdotal evidence as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Fight for Privacy, Apple vs. FBI</title>
      <link>/post/the-fight-for-privacy-apple-vs-fbi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-fight-for-privacy-apple-vs-fbi/</guid>
      <description>For those of you that have been living under a rock, the FBI and Apple have been engaged in a legal battle over unlocking the iPhone of the terrorist in the San Bernadino attack. The FBI wants to get into the phone to further investigate the attack, having already previously obtained a warrant. However, they cannot get into the phone since there is a pass code. It&amp;rsquo;s a newer model phone with built-in encryption and investigators are worried the data would be wiped if they tried to get access to the phone by brute force&amp;ndash;10,000 combinations and the phone will probably wipe itself after 10 tries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bernie Sanders, Millennials, and Why They Are Wrong...About Everything</title>
      <link>/post/bernie-sanders-millennials-and-why-they-are-wrong-about-everything/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/bernie-sanders-millennials-and-why-they-are-wrong-about-everything/</guid>
      <description>Some of you are going to love this post. Most of you will hate it. My job is to ell the truth. Sometimes the truth hurts, and some of you can&amp;rsquo;t handle the truth. However, the truth shall set you free. I&amp;rsquo;m out of clichés.
Bernie Sanders is an admitted &amp;ldquo;democratic socialist&amp;rdquo;. There used to be a time not that long ago where socialism was proven to be a very bad thing in America and one step away from communism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Obligatory Johnny Football Post</title>
      <link>/post/the-obligatory-johnny-football-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-obligatory-johnny-football-post/</guid>
      <description>It has been reported that the Cleveland Browns will release Johnny Manziel on March 9. Normally, the release of a Cleveland Browns&amp;rsquo; quarterback comes after a horrible two to three year tenure and is accompanied by a new coach, general manager, or both. Lather, rinse, repeat.
Manziel is different though. He isn&amp;rsquo;t being released for being crappy on the field. We don&amp;rsquo;t know if he is a good quarterback, bad quarterback, mediocre quarterback or anything else.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do Black Lives Matter?</title>
      <link>/post/do-black-lives-matter/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/do-black-lives-matter/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t watch shows like Family Guy, The Simpsons, South Park, etc. They&amp;rsquo;re usually full of trash and (mostly) liberal propaganda. However, even a blind squirrel can find a nut every once in a while. A clip from an episode of Family Guy went viral last month.
  Peter Griffin: Everyone! Everyone! Listen, I have something to say. Cleveland Jr. Doesn&amp;rsquo;t deserve any of this. All those things you heard about Cleveland Jr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mega Jackpot, Mega Problems</title>
      <link>/post/mega-jackpot-mega-problems/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/mega-jackpot-mega-problems/</guid>
      <description>In case you&amp;rsquo;ve missed the news, the Powerball jackpot is now up to $1.5 billion. That&amp;rsquo;s BILLION with a B.
$1,500,000,000.
Yowzer!!! That&amp;rsquo;s a lot of money. Life altering money. And yet, it won&amp;rsquo;t change a thing. Every single one of you reading this who decides to play won&amp;rsquo;t win. I can safely say that given that the odds of winning are 1 in 292 million. For whoever does win, problems will come with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flat Tax vs. Fair Tax</title>
      <link>/post/flat-tax-vs-fair-tax/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/flat-tax-vs-fair-tax/</guid>
      <description>Republican Presidential candidate and retired neurosurgeon Dr. Ben Carson is proposing a 14.9% flat income tax and throwing out the current tax code. The primary arguments made for going to a flat tax is simple: there will be no loopholes for anyone to jump through and take advantage of, no one will be taxed twice on capital gains, interest and dividends, and most citizens will have some skin in the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Left vs. Right</title>
      <link>/post/left-vs-right/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/left-vs-right/</guid>
      <description>Prager University recently did a five video series on the different perspectives of the left and right on some key fundamental issues. I encourage everyone to watch the videos posted below but I&amp;rsquo;ll provide a quick take on each one.
1. The Size of Government  The best place to start is with this one. What is the role of government in our lives? I think the U.S. federal government has only a few rights and responsibilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Corruption of the DNC</title>
      <link>/post/the-corruption-of-the-dnc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-corruption-of-the-dnc/</guid>
      <description>Hillary Clinton, Martin O&amp;rsquo;Malley, and Bernie Sanders&amp;hellip;three people who will never be president
Disclaimer: I am NOT a Democrat. I am not endorsing any Democrats at all. I am not supporting Hillary Clinton, Bernie Sanders, and Martin O&amp;rsquo;Malley and I hope the Democratic nominee gets destroyed in the general election. None of them are capable of fixing this country.
Now that the disclaimer is out of the way&amp;hellip;
Bernie Sanders is getting screwed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diverging Roads</title>
      <link>/post/diverging-roads/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/diverging-roads/</guid>
      <description>Most of us have friends we went to elementary, middle, and/or high school with that we haven&amp;rsquo;t seen in a long, long time. We sometimes ask ourselves where they are and what have they done with their lives. Where would we likely stumble upon them? In the middle of downtown? On a bus? At a restaurant? A reunion?
How about on opposite sides of a courtroom?
 Judge Mindy Glazer came across Arthur Booth, an old middle school friend at a bail hearing in Florida.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The End of &#39;No Child Left Behind&#39;</title>
      <link>/post/the-end-of-no-child-left-behind/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-end-of-no-child-left-behind/</guid>
      <description>So a few days ago, the &amp;ldquo;Every Student Succeeds Act&amp;rdquo; was signed into law after passing the House and Senate with broad bipartisan support, a rarity in recent times. This law does away with most of the regulations that were put into place with &amp;ldquo;No Child Left Behind&amp;rdquo; and returns a lot of the power in regards to education policy back to the states. As a result, the strict pressures in testing students to receive federal funding is removed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating Black Conservatives</title>
      <link>/post/creating-black-conservatives/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/creating-black-conservatives/</guid>
      <description>Barack Obama won over 90% of the black vote in the 2008 and 2012 presidential elections. In addition, Democrats routinely win at least 80% of the black vote in every election on every level. Yet black people have struggled for generations to get ahead while every other group has. This leads to an obvious question:
Why don&amp;rsquo;t blacks vote conservative?
Or perhaps the real question is why do blacks not consider any republican, independent, or any third party but vote for Democrats in droves?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Three F&#39;s</title>
      <link>/post/the-three-f-s/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-three-f-s/</guid>
      <description>Another Thanksgiving has come and gone here in America. And for another year, this great holiday where we are to be thankful for what God has provided us with has once again fallen into commercialization. Thanksgiving has devolved into the three F&amp;rsquo;s:
Food, Family, and Football
People flocked to places near and far to gather together with family members (along with a few friends) to prepare and enjoy a scrumptious feast consisting of one plate (or two, three, or sometimes four) plates of food.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More Radical Islamic Terrorism</title>
      <link>/post/more-radical-islamic-terrorism/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/more-radical-islamic-terrorism/</guid>
      <description>Over two years ago, I wrote a post after an attack in London in regards to radical Islam. I called out President Obama for not calling out radical Islam. He refuses to use those words. In fact, he referred to ISIS as a JV team in 2014. Even after the Charlie Hebdo attack in January 2015, President Obama refused to acknowledge that the real problem isn&amp;rsquo;t the people, but the religion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Safe Spaces</title>
      <link>/post/safe-spaces/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/safe-spaces/</guid>
      <description>Safe Space: A place where anyone can relax and be fully self-expressed, without fear of being made to feel uncomfortable, unwelcome, or unsafe on account of biological sex, race/ethnicity, sexual orientation, gender identity or expression, cultural background, age, or physical or mental ability; a place where the rules guard each person&amp;rsquo;s self-respect and dignity and strongly encourage everyone to respect others
 WHAT??!!!!
Where did this come from and why are these popping up all over college campuses in America?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baby Mama and Baby Daddy</title>
      <link>/post/baby-mama-and-baby-daddy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/baby-mama-and-baby-daddy/</guid>
      <description>Maury, Steve Wilkos, Jeremy Kyle, Trisha, Paternity Court&amp;hellip; The list goes on. A lot of hours per day on daytime TV is spent dealing with paternity tests. Thousands of children who don&amp;rsquo;t know who their father is. Thousands of women testing thousands of men so they can find their &amp;ldquo;baby&amp;rsquo;s daddy&amp;rdquo;. Thousands of men who don&amp;rsquo;t want to deal with &amp;ldquo;baby mama drama&amp;rdquo;. Even if the episode isn&amp;rsquo;t about paternity, there are at least two &amp;ldquo;adults&amp;rdquo; involved in issues that break up relationships (if it isn&amp;rsquo;t already broken) where these adults happen to have children involved.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Role of the Media in 21st Century America</title>
      <link>/post/the-role-of-the-media-in-21st-century-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-role-of-the-media-in-21st-century-america/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Congress shall make no law respecting an establishment of religion, or prohibiting the free exercise thereof; or abridging the freedom of speech, or of the press; or the right of the people peaceably to assemble, and to petition the Government for a redress of grievances.&amp;rdquo;
1st Amendment of the United States Constitution
 That&amp;rsquo;s a mouthful right there. I&amp;rsquo;m not going to go into detail as to what all of this means.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michael Vick, Dog Fighting, and Forgiveness</title>
      <link>/post/michael-vick-dog-fighting-and-forgiveness/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/michael-vick-dog-fighting-and-forgiveness/</guid>
      <description>I didn&amp;rsquo;t think I would need to write this post. This subject was exhausted over the summer and wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be a relevant subject again unless the unthinkable happens&amp;hellip;
NOOOO!!!!
It&amp;rsquo;s Mike Vick time in Pittsburgh.
So everybody has their concerns for one of two reasons. Either they don&amp;rsquo;t think he can play anymore if he ever could play, or they harp on his past with dogfighting. If someone is worried about the Steelers and Michael Vick for football-related reasons (can&amp;rsquo;t throw accurately, turns the ball over, always injured, too old, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Most Wonderful Time of the Year</title>
      <link>/post/the-most-wonderful-time-of-the-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-most-wonderful-time-of-the-year/</guid>
      <description>Trick or treat! Did you think I was talking about the Christmas season? Of course not! Fall is by far my favorite season of the year and it has finally come around again. The leaves falling from the trees in a variety of color, the smell of apple cider, the harvest of the fruits and vegetables, hay rides, cooler weather&amp;hellip;AND EVERY SINGLE MAJOR SPORTS LEAGUE IN ACTION!
It&amp;rsquo;s the beginning of both basketball and hockey season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iranian Hackers</title>
      <link>/post/iranian-hackers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/iranian-hackers/</guid>
      <description>So a couple days ago when I was about to make a post when I found that my website was compromised by Iranian hackers. My content was still there but you had to scroll halfway down the page through some obscene material. If anyone saw that, I greatly apologize. It seems as though I was hacked for a couple of weeks before I noticed. That&amp;rsquo;s what happens when you don&amp;rsquo;t keep up with stuff&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digging Up the Past</title>
      <link>/post/digging-up-the-past/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/digging-up-the-past/</guid>
      <description>I thought we were over this. I thought we learned our lesson and moved on. I thought there were more important things going on in the world that required our time attention.
I thought wrong.
Out of all of the lessons and actions that could have possibly been taken after the Charleston church shooting, Americans choose to turn their anger, not towards the person (the conservative response) or towards guns (the liberal response), but towards a flag.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Da Beats, Vol. 1</title>
      <link>/post/da-beats-vol-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/da-beats-vol-1/</guid>
      <description>I’m sure most of us have some hobbies that we do on the side. Some are things people know about and allow us to indulge in. Others include hidden sides that few, if any, may know. For me, this hidden side is poetry. I engaged in it little when I was in high school and college but have put it off to the side for a few years. However, I’ve come up with a few pieces recently that I would like to share.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Broken Promise, A Broken Dream</title>
      <link>/post/a-broken-promise-a-broken-dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/a-broken-promise-a-broken-dream/</guid>
      <description>For some of you who used to follow my old rambling and rants that I posted on Myspace (yeah, I know) and Facebook from the late 2000s, you may remember how often I went off on black people. I made a promise to never again use my forum to discuss issues about the black community. It’s not that I wanted to avoid confrontation. I just got sick and tired of writing about the same old thing over and over and over and over and over and over again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s Time</title>
      <link>/post/it-s-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/it-s-time/</guid>
      <description>Yep. I’m making the leap. I’ve thought about doing it for about three years now. I’ve spent plenty of time praying about it and exploring the options available to me. However, I’m not going to get anywhere by thinking about it. I’m at a standstill while everything is passing me by. It’ll be tough, but if God wants it to be, it’ll be.
After all, if God gave someone a gift, an ability, or a tool that very few people had and he didn’t use it, wouldn’t he be disappointing God?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Truth Shall Come Out</title>
      <link>/post/the-truth-shall-come-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-truth-shall-come-out/</guid>
      <description>So a select committee has finally been formed to investigate Benghazi…20 months and one Presidential election after the attack. There are STILL questions that we are still awaiting honest answers for. I think the family members of the victims deserve answers more. In no particular order:
Why did we still have people in Benghazi after every other foreign entity, including the Red Cross, left due to safety concerns?
Why was security not increased after previous attacks on the consulate in April 2012 and on the International Red Cross office in May 2012?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When Freedom of Speech is No Longer Free</title>
      <link>/post/when-freedom-of-speech-is-no-longer-free/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/when-freedom-of-speech-is-no-longer-free/</guid>
      <description>Note: This is NOT an endorsement on the comments made by Los Angeles Clippers owner Donald Sterling.
So Clippers owner Donald Sterling was fined $2.5 million and banned from the NBA for life. There wasn’t even as much as a hint of an investigation before this was handed down. What did he do to warrant this harsh punishment? Did he beat his wife? Did he kill someone? Is he a serial rapist?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Undecided Left</title>
      <link>/post/the-undecided-left/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-undecided-left/</guid>
      <description>So mainstream media believes there is a battle on the right between Tea Party Conservatives and the establishment Republicans? They hype this disagreement and site this division as to why the Democratic Party will prevail in the 2014 elections. Their story is that the Tea Party is too “extreme” and too “radical” for mainstream Republicans and Independents to get behind. The likes of MSNBC, NBC, ABC, and CBS are saying that Jeb Bush and Chris Christie are biggest challengers on the Republican ticket for the 2016 presidential elections (Child, please!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Martin, Zimmerman, and Race</title>
      <link>/post/martin-zimmerman-and-race/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/martin-zimmerman-and-race/</guid>
      <description>As a “black” man, I’m supposed to be obligated to comment on this case. I’m supposed to be outraged that an innocent, unarmed child carrying Skittles and iced tea was targeted and killed because of the color of his skin. I’m supposed to be outraged because this “white hispanic” wannabe cop got away with murder. I’m supposed to stand by my race. I’m supposed to believe the jury got it wrong.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Isn&#39;t Illegal Immigration...Illegal?</title>
      <link>/post/isn-t-illegal-immigration-illegal/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/isn-t-illegal-immigration-illegal/</guid>
      <description>Let me be frank. All Americans should be against any version of amnesty. We have at least 11 million illegal immigrants here (most likely more). By any other standard, that’s an enemy invasion. A lot of these people sneaking in are low wage workers who don’t contribute anything to this country. These illegal aliens are taking jobs away that usually go to teenagers and low-skill workers. This is coming at a time when the 16-24 unemployment rate is officially at 13.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I&#39;m a Conservative</title>
      <link>/post/why-i-m-a-conservative/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/why-i-m-a-conservative/</guid>
      <description>So some of my friends have criticized me for being a conservative. They go on to site how much damage and suffering African-Americans have gone through because of conservatives or how conservatives are made up of rich, racist, old white men. Or they complain about conservatives clinging to their guns and Bibles and having “outdated” morals and traditions.
Nothing can be further from the truth.
I’m a conservative because I am against big government.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Radical Islamic Terrorism</title>
      <link>/post/radical-islamic-terrorism/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/radical-islamic-terrorism/</guid>
      <description>This past week, a British solider was hacked to death by two terrorists. For more information, (VIEWERS DISCRETION ADVISED!) please check it out. This solider was hacked and stabbed to death. The two guys were shouting “Allahu Akbar!” in the process. Afterwards, these two men were allowed to walk around for at least 20 minutes before police showed up to the scene. During that time period, one of the men walked up to a camera and clearly explained his reasoning:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m Back</title>
      <link>/post/i-m-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/i-m-back/</guid>
      <description>So I am back to blogging. No Blogger this time. As much as I loved the ease and convenience, I needed my own website with my own flexibility. With that being said, this platform requires me to be a bit more engaged to writing and posting on social media. My first new post should be up soon. If there is anything you want me to discuss in particular, please feel free to comment below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uninformed or Uncaring</title>
      <link>/post/uninformed-or-uncaring/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/uninformed-or-uncaring/</guid>
      <description>NOTE: THIS IS NOT AN ENDORSEMENT OF THE DEMOCRATIC PARTY!
Let me get this straight. The City of Pittsburgh has a population of 307,000. There are 175,000 Democrats who outnumber Republicans 5 to 1. In a city that has been ran by the Democratic Party for over half a century, only 44,000 turned out. That’s 25%. Bill Peduto won the Democratic nomination with 52% of the vote. 22,800 voters is only 13% of the total number of registered Democrats.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>