<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>football on Ranting Robert</title>
    <link>/tags/football/</link>
    <description>Recent content in football on Ranting Robert</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© This post is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License，please give source if you likes to quote or reproduce.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/football/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Power of Roger Goodell</title>
      <link>/post/the-power-of-roger-goodell/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-power-of-roger-goodell/</guid>
      <description>![] (https://i.kinja-img.com/gawker-media/image/upload/s--wY6nEutB--/c_fill%2Cfl_progressive%2Cg_center%2Ch_450%2Cq_80%2Cw_800/18xwcs6tyh0kmjpg.jpg)
When Roger Goodell succeeded Paul Tagliabue as NFL commissioner in 2006, players getting into trouble off the field was become a major problem. With players like Adam &amp;ldquo;Pacman&amp;rdquo; Jones and Chris Henry getting arrested every other week and a multitude of other players committing various legal infractions going unpunished by the league, it appeared as though a firm hand was needed. [Long-term suspensions] (https://www.espn.com/nfl/news/story?id=2832015) for Jones and Henry in 2007 seemed to send a message that improper behavior was no longer tolerated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Martavis?  Why?</title>
      <link>/post/why-martavis-why/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/why-martavis-why/</guid>
      <description>Once upon a time, there was a wide receiver who was very talented physically but had some issues of the field. He liked to smoke marijuana in his free time. An NFL team decided to take a chance on him and he was able to put up big numbers on the field as a rookie. However, he was suspended for a few games before his second year in the league. The troubled wide receiver promised to clean up his act and returned to dominating on the field after returning for suspension.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Obligatory Johnny Football Post</title>
      <link>/post/the-obligatory-johnny-football-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-obligatory-johnny-football-post/</guid>
      <description>![] (https://media2.newsnet5.com/photo/2015/10/16/Police_Report__Johnny_Manziel_pulled_ove_3577540001_25331367_ver1.0_640_480.jpg)
It has been reported that the Cleveland Browns will release Johnny Manziel on March 9. Normally, the release of a Cleveland Browns&amp;rsquo; quarterback comes after a horrible two to three year tenure and is accompanied by a new coach, general manager, or both. Lather, rinse, repeat.
Manziel is different though. He isn&#39;t being released for being crappy on the field. We don&#39;t know if he is a good quarterback, bad quarterback, mediocre quarterback or anything else.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Three F&#39;s</title>
      <link>/post/the-three-f-s/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-three-f-s/</guid>
      <description>Another Thanksgiving has come and gone here in America. And for another year, this great holiday where we are to be thankful for what God has provided us with has once again fallen into commercialization. Thanksgiving has devolved into the three F&#39;s:
Food, Family, and Football
People flocked to places near and far to gather together with family members (along with a few friends) to prepare and enjoy a scrumptious feast consisting of one plate (or two, three, or sometimes four) plates of food.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michael Vick, Dog Fighting, and Forgiveness</title>
      <link>/post/michael-vick-dog-fighting-and-forgiveness/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/michael-vick-dog-fighting-and-forgiveness/</guid>
      <description>I didn&#39;t think I would need to write this post. This subject was exhausted over the summer and wouldn&#39;t be a relevant subject again unless the unthinkable happens&amp;hellip;
NOOOO!!!!
It&#39;s Mike Vick time in Pittsburgh.
So everybody has their concerns for one of two reasons. Either they don&#39;t think he can play anymore if he ever could play, or they harp on his past with dogfighting. If someone is worried about the Steelers and Michael Vick for football-related reasons (can&#39;t throw accurately, turns the ball over, always injured, too old, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>