<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Religion on Ranting Robert</title>
    <link>/tags/religion/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Religion on Ranting Robert</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© This post is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License，please give source if you likes to quote or reproduce.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/religion/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>More Radical Islamic Terrorism</title>
      <link>/post/more-radical-islamic-terrorism/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/more-radical-islamic-terrorism/</guid>
      <description>Over two years ago, I wrote a post after an attack in London in regards to radical Islam. I called out President Obama for not calling out radical Islam. He refuses to use those words. In fact, he referred to ISIS as a JV team in 2014. Even after the Charlie Hebdo attack in January 2015, President Obama refused to acknowledge that the real problem isn&amp;rsquo;t the people, but the religion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When Freedom of Speech is No Longer Free</title>
      <link>/post/when-freedom-of-speech-is-no-longer-free/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/when-freedom-of-speech-is-no-longer-free/</guid>
      <description>Note: This is NOT an endorsement on the comments made by Los Angeles Clippers owner Donald Sterling.
So Clippers owner Donald Sterling was fined $2.5 million and banned from the NBA for life. There wasn’t even as much as a hint of an investigation before this was handed down. What did he do to warrant this harsh punishment? Did he beat his wife? Did he kill someone? Is he a serial rapist?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Undecided Left</title>
      <link>/post/the-undecided-left/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-undecided-left/</guid>
      <description>So mainstream media believes there is a battle on the right between Tea Party Conservatives and the establishment Republicans? They hype this disagreement and site this division as to why the Democratic Party will prevail in the 2014 elections. Their story is that the Tea Party is too “extreme” and too “radical” for mainstream Republicans and Independents to get behind. The likes of MSNBC, NBC, ABC, and CBS are saying that Jeb Bush and Chris Christie are biggest challengers on the Republican ticket for the 2016 presidential elections (Child, please!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>