<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>sports on Ranting Robert</title>
    <link>/tags/sports/</link>
    <description>Recent content in sports on Ranting Robert</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© This post is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License. Please source if you like to quote or reproduce.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/sports/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Power of Roger Goodell</title>
      <link>/post/the-power-of-roger-goodell/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-power-of-roger-goodell/</guid>
      <description>![] (https://i.kinja-img.com/gawker-media/image/upload/s--wY6nEutB--/c_fill%2Cfl_progressive%2Cg_center%2Ch_450%2Cq_80%2Cw_800/18xwcs6tyh0kmjpg.jpg)
When Roger Goodell succeeded Paul Tagliabue as NFL commissioner in 2006, players getting into trouble off the field was become a major problem. With players like Adam &amp;ldquo;Pacman&amp;rdquo; Jones and Chris Henry getting arrested every other week and a multitude of other players committing various legal infractions going unpunished by the league, it appeared as though a firm hand was needed. [Long-term suspensions] (https://www.espn.com/nfl/news/story?id=2832015) for Jones and Henry in 2007 seemed to send a message that improper behavior was no longer tolerated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Obligatory Johnny Football Post</title>
      <link>/post/the-obligatory-johnny-football-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-obligatory-johnny-football-post/</guid>
      <description>![] (https://media2.newsnet5.com/photo/2015/10/16/Police_Report__Johnny_Manziel_pulled_ove_3577540001_25331367_ver1.0_640_480.jpg)
It has been reported that the Cleveland Browns will release Johnny Manziel on March 9. Normally, the release of a Cleveland Browns&amp;rsquo; quarterback comes after a horrible two to three year tenure and is accompanied by a new coach, general manager, or both. Lather, rinse, repeat.
Manziel is different though. He isn&#39;t being released for being crappy on the field. We don&#39;t know if he is a good quarterback, bad quarterback, mediocre quarterback or anything else.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When Freedom of Speech is No Longer Free</title>
      <link>/post/when-freedom-of-speech-is-no-longer-free/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/when-freedom-of-speech-is-no-longer-free/</guid>
      <description>Note: This is NOT an endorsement on the comments made by Los Angeles Clippers owner Donald Sterling.
So Clippers owner Donald Sterling was fined $2.5 million and banned from the NBA for life. There wasn’t even as much as a hint of an investigation before this was handed down. What did he do to warrant this harsh punishment? Did he beat his wife? Did he kill someone? Is he a serial rapist?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>