<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Race on Ranting Robert</title>
    <link>/tags/race/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Race on Ranting Robert</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© This post is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License，please give source if you likes to quote or reproduce.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/race/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Wendy Bell and the Outrage of Black Pittsburgh</title>
      <link>/post/wendy-bell-and-the-outrage-of-black-pittsburgh/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/wendy-bell-and-the-outrage-of-black-pittsburgh/</guid>
      <description>Trigger Warning: This post contains truthful information that may be offensive or sensitive to certain segments of the population such as college students, liberals, and blacks. I am not responsible for any hurt feelings this may cause. Of course, I don&amp;rsquo;t care about your feelings.
Pittsburgh reporter Wendy Bell was fired from WTAE after making some controversial remarks on her Facebook page after a recent shooting. As we all know, when we talk about controversy and black people, it usually means black people don&amp;rsquo;t like what someone else said about them because it&amp;rsquo;s the truth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Pointless Debate</title>
      <link>/post/the-pointless-debate/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-pointless-debate/</guid>
      <description>Over the last 10-20 years, I have had many heated political discussions with people of different colors, different backgrounds, and different walks of life. Social media has made it easier to have these discussions and meet all kinds of people. When having such discussions, my goal is to be as clear minded and rational as possible when arguing my point of view while trying to use as much anecdotal evidence as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do Black Lives Matter?</title>
      <link>/post/do-black-lives-matter/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/do-black-lives-matter/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t watch shows like Family Guy, The Simpsons, South Park, etc. They&amp;rsquo;re usually full of trash and (mostly) liberal propaganda. However, even a blind squirrel can find a nut every once in a while. A clip from an episode of Family Guy went viral last month.
  Peter Griffin: Everyone! Everyone! Listen, I have something to say. Cleveland Jr. Doesn&amp;rsquo;t deserve any of this. All those things you heard about Cleveland Jr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Safe Spaces</title>
      <link>/post/safe-spaces/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/safe-spaces/</guid>
      <description>Safe Space: A place where anyone can relax and be fully self-expressed, without fear of being made to feel uncomfortable, unwelcome, or unsafe on account of biological sex, race/ethnicity, sexual orientation, gender identity or expression, cultural background, age, or physical or mental ability; a place where the rules guard each person&amp;rsquo;s self-respect and dignity and strongly encourage everyone to respect others
 WHAT??!!!!
Where did this come from and why are these popping up all over college campuses in America?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Broken Promise, A Broken Dream</title>
      <link>/post/a-broken-promise-a-broken-dream/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/a-broken-promise-a-broken-dream/</guid>
      <description>For some of you who used to follow my old rambling and rants that I posted on Myspace (yeah, I know) and Facebook from the late 2000s, you may remember how often I went off on black people. I made a promise to never again use my forum to discuss issues about the black community. It’s not that I wanted to avoid confrontation. I just got sick and tired of writing about the same old thing over and over and over and over and over and over again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When Freedom of Speech is No Longer Free</title>
      <link>/post/when-freedom-of-speech-is-no-longer-free/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/when-freedom-of-speech-is-no-longer-free/</guid>
      <description>Note: This is NOT an endorsement on the comments made by Los Angeles Clippers owner Donald Sterling.
So Clippers owner Donald Sterling was fined $2.5 million and banned from the NBA for life. There wasn’t even as much as a hint of an investigation before this was handed down. What did he do to warrant this harsh punishment? Did he beat his wife? Did he kill someone? Is he a serial rapist?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Undecided Left</title>
      <link>/post/the-undecided-left/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-undecided-left/</guid>
      <description>So mainstream media believes there is a battle on the right between Tea Party Conservatives and the establishment Republicans? They hype this disagreement and site this division as to why the Democratic Party will prevail in the 2014 elections. Their story is that the Tea Party is too “extreme” and too “radical” for mainstream Republicans and Independents to get behind. The likes of MSNBC, NBC, ABC, and CBS are saying that Jeb Bush and Chris Christie are biggest challengers on the Republican ticket for the 2016 presidential elections (Child, please!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Martin, Zimmerman, and Race</title>
      <link>/post/martin-zimmerman-and-race/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/martin-zimmerman-and-race/</guid>
      <description>As a “black” man, I’m supposed to be obligated to comment on this case. I’m supposed to be outraged that an innocent, unarmed child carrying Skittles and iced tea was targeted and killed because of the color of his skin. I’m supposed to be outraged because this “white hispanic” wannabe cop got away with murder. I’m supposed to stand by my race. I’m supposed to believe the jury got it wrong.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>