<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Steelers on Ranting Robert</title>
    <link>/tags/steelers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Steelers on Ranting Robert</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© This post is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License，please give source if you likes to quote or reproduce.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/steelers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Power of Roger Goodell</title>
      <link>/post/the-power-of-roger-goodell/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-power-of-roger-goodell/</guid>
      <description>![] (https://i.kinja-img.com/gawker-media/image/upload/s--wY6nEutB--/c_fill%2Cfl_progressive%2Cg_center%2Ch_450%2Cq_80%2Cw_800/18xwcs6tyh0kmjpg.jpg)
When Roger Goodell succeeded Paul Tagliabue as NFL commissioner in 2006, players getting into trouble off the field was become a major problem. With players like Adam &amp;ldquo;Pacman&amp;rdquo; Jones and Chris Henry getting arrested every other week and a multitude of other players committing various legal infractions going unpunished by the league, it appeared as though a firm hand was needed. [Long-term suspensions] (https://www.espn.com/nfl/news/story?id=2832015) for Jones and Henry in 2007 seemed to send a message that improper behavior was no longer tolerated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Martavis?  Why?</title>
      <link>/post/why-martavis-why/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/why-martavis-why/</guid>
      <description>Once upon a time, there was a wide receiver who was very talented physically but had some issues of the field. He liked to smoke marijuana in his free time. An NFL team decided to take a chance on him and he was able to put up big numbers on the field as a rookie. However, he was suspended for a few games before his second year in the league. The troubled wide receiver promised to clean up his act and returned to dominating on the field after returning for suspension.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>