<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Government on Ranting Robert</title>
    <link>/tags/government/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Government on Ranting Robert</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© This post is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License，please give source if you likes to quote or reproduce.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/government/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Fight for Privacy, Apple vs. FBI</title>
      <link>/post/the-fight-for-privacy-apple-vs-fbi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-fight-for-privacy-apple-vs-fbi/</guid>
      <description>For those of you that have been living under a rock, the FBI and Apple have been engaged in a legal battle over unlocking the iPhone of the terrorist in the San Bernadino attack. The FBI wants to get into the phone to further investigate the attack, having already previously obtained a warrant. However, they cannot get into the phone since there is a pass code. It&amp;rsquo;s a newer model phone with built-in encryption and investigators are worried the data would be wiped if they tried to get access to the phone by brute force&amp;ndash;10,000 combinations and the phone will probably wipe itself after 10 tries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flat Tax vs. Fair Tax</title>
      <link>/post/flat-tax-vs-fair-tax/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/flat-tax-vs-fair-tax/</guid>
      <description>Republican Presidential candidate and retired neurosurgeon Dr. Ben Carson is proposing a 14.9% flat income tax and throwing out the current tax code. The primary arguments made for going to a flat tax is simple: there will be no loopholes for anyone to jump through and take advantage of, no one will be taxed twice on capital gains, interest and dividends, and most citizens will have some skin in the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Undecided Left</title>
      <link>/post/the-undecided-left/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/the-undecided-left/</guid>
      <description>So mainstream media believes there is a battle on the right between Tea Party Conservatives and the establishment Republicans? They hype this disagreement and site this division as to why the Democratic Party will prevail in the 2014 elections. Their story is that the Tea Party is too “extreme” and too “radical” for mainstream Republicans and Independents to get behind. The likes of MSNBC, NBC, ABC, and CBS are saying that Jeb Bush and Chris Christie are biggest challengers on the Republican ticket for the 2016 presidential elections (Child, please!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>